

Nguyen Thi Phuong Thao

Medical Representative

CONTACT INFORMATION

- **1** 01/12/1993
- Female
- **** 01628295148
- nguyenthao.pharma.cm.vn@gmail.com
- ♥ số 51, đường số 5, cư xá Bình Thới, quận 11,TPHCM, Vietnam
- i https://www.facebook.com/phuongthaocm12

OBJECTIVE

Apply the experience and skills when working in the hospital, understand doctors and staffs in hospital. From it help find customers and expand the customers, become a professional sales staff and bring a lot value to customers. From that, I will contribute to development of Company.

SKILLS

Logical thinking and creative

Public Speaking

INTERESTS

Gym

Badminton

EDUCATION

08/2012 - 08/2017

Can Tho University of Medicine and Pharmacy

Major: Pharmacist

Graduation: Good, average grade 7.93

WORK EXPERIENCE

07/2015 - 09/2015

Thanh Vu Medic Bac Lieu Hospital

Intern in drugstore's hospital

- Taking medicine, consulting patients in pharmacies
- Supporting monthly pharmacy inventory
- Supporting to order drugs, contact the company.

08/2017 - 08/2018

Thanh Vu Medic Bac Lieu Hospital

Staff in faculty of pharmacy

- -Write drug information on the clinic wed site and issue drug information.
- -Answer questions from doctors when communicating directly or by phone and email.
- -Supporting to make monthly inventory report.

CERTIFICATIONS

Certificate A in Technology information (Can Tho University)

Certificate A in English (Can Tho University)V 2013